<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conrad&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://conrads.website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Conrad&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://conrads.website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Listing</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/list/</guid>
      <description>I need a list of all the things I had bene thinking of working on so that I can keep track of what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to organize. In a loose GTD fashion, &amp;ldquo;Things I Can Do Now&amp;rdquo; will be listed near the top
 Other things are listed on project-plans&amp;hellip;
   M2A2 Case
  Review Accounts
 Student Loans Spotify Youtube Amazon    Department Letter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/time/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot I want to talk about, but I know that I&amp;rsquo;m just creating more work for myself down the road.
I have made a few of recordings of Quantity vs Quality and on 20/80 happiness-scheduling, but I need to start writing these things out.
Upon opening this blog, I found a a nice surprise waiting for me.
I finally got around to figuring out how NixOS aliasing works, and added an alias for nix-shell to ns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing with Consensus</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/js-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 12:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/js-test/</guid>
      <description>This is largely an exercise in using LaTex, Pandoc, and p5js to try and describe a problem and potential solutions.
  Problem with election process for managing service knowledge in a cluster
  Explain SWIM, Serf, PAXOS
  Explain new purpose of adapting experiment projects into blog components
  HTML and PDF views?
 I need to break the PDF apart so that graphs, LaTeX, and Tikz drawing can be added to the Hugo doc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Plans</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/project-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/project-plans/</guid>
      <description>As briefly described in my previous post, I need to get my projects organized. This page &amp;lsquo;might&amp;rsquo; be a living page and get updated as needed.
(Or, I may simply copy and paste it whenever I make changes. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure which yet.)
I know that I&amp;rsquo;m missing some items here, but my objective is just to get these posted so that I can visualize and identify what I would like to do first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Blogging and What&#39;s Next</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/on-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/on-blogging/</guid>
      <description>(I&amp;rsquo;m not a very good blogger.)
In lieu of blogging, I have been researching and soul searching for new and &amp;ldquo;better&amp;rdquo; ways of sharing personal information like images and my thoughts. I like writing but I want more control over my potential audience. Technical posts and descriptions of life events seem to be fine concepts for a blog, but I write about so much more than these topics.
When I first deployed this website, I used Hugo (link in the footer) and a few bash scripts that encrypted my documents with a PGP key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accuracy x Time</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/accuracy-x-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/accuracy-x-time/</guid>
      <description>Freewriting for 20minutes - mistrakes galore!
 One of my more recent goals is to abandon the idea of &amp;lsquo;projects&amp;rsquo; as a categorical method for organizing tasks and time. There are a few ideas that all relate to this;
 Projects are too goal oriented, they cause us to lean into analysis paralysis and we get overburdened by perfectionism. &amp;lsquo;My Project is too personal to take shortcuts! That&amp;rsquo;s not who I am!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi Zero Cluster Storage</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 23:22:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/cluster/</guid>
      <description>Physical Build The physical considerations of the project must meet needs of future-proofing, cost, and setup time requirements. The aim of such a project would be to achieve:
 Reliable, RAID-like cloud storage and computing Cheap storage Expandability Intelligent software design  Cluster Hat The Cluster Hat is a deivce that connects multiple Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s together rather simply and gracefully. It connects and powers the Zero&amp;rsquo;s mini USB port, and evern includes a software bundle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Shells</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/more-shells/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 09:51:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/more-shells/</guid>
      <description>Well I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty busy recently, as the semester winds down the workload typically ramps up&amp;hellip; So it goes.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to find the time to write here more, and sometimes I have. It&amp;rsquo;s just that so many of my words end up being for me and me alone, and because of that this place continues to look empty&amp;hellip;
Well, to help fight the emptiness, here are some shell renders I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Seashells</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/posts/seashells/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/posts/seashells/</guid>
      <description>In Seashells: The Plainness and Beauty of their Mathematical Description, Jorge Picado describes the mathematics necessary to simulate the shape of a multitude of different seashells. In this post, I wanted to share some renders I created while implementing Picado&amp;rsquo;s math into SciView and how the fourteen parameters function.
Defining the Spiral The parameters D, A, alpha and beta allow us to construct any variety of spiral we want.
D specifies the chirality of the seashell - which direction it spirals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume - September 2020</title>
      <link>https://conrads.website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conrads.website/about/</guid>
      <description>This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>